<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Hope Community Fellowship</title><link>https://hcftesting.hacdan.org/</link><description>Recent content on Hope Community Fellowship</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://hcftesting.hacdan.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://hcftesting.hacdan.org/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hcftesting.hacdan.org/contact/</guid><description>Visit us at 973 Nortontown Road, Addison VT
Need to chat? Give us a call (802) 349 - 9380
Prefer email? Go for it! hcfpastor@yahoo.com
Need to send us a letter? We&amp;rsquo;re all eyes! Hope Community Fellowship - 2867 Mountain Road, Addison VT 05491</description></item><item><title>Good News</title><link>https://hcftesting.hacdan.org/goodnews/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hcftesting.hacdan.org/goodnews/</guid><description>Good News - God&amp;rsquo;s Plan of Salvation Here&amp;rsquo;s the best news in the world&amp;ndash;God loves us so much that He offered Jesus on the cross to bring us back into relationship with Him. You can begin a relationship with Jesus anywhere at any time.
Whoever calls on the name of the Lord shall be saved. (Romans 10:13)
It has been called the ABC&amp;rsquo;s of Salvation, which is very fitting because we have been called by God to have a child-like faith.</description></item><item><title>Mission Statement</title><link>https://hcftesting.hacdan.org/missionstatement/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hcftesting.hacdan.org/missionstatement/</guid><description>As a church family we strive to obey the Bible Bringing people to Jesus and Membership in His family Developing them to Christlike Maturity Equipping them for their Ministry in the Church And life Mission, in order to Magnify God&amp;rsquo;s Name We believe this is accomplished through literal Bible interpretation, and obedience to the Word of God.
We, for our part, proclaim him, we warn, confront, and teach everyone in all wisdom; so that we may present everyone as having reached the goal, united with the Messiah.</description></item><item><title>What to expect on your first visit</title><link>https://hcftesting.hacdan.org/whattoexpect/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hcftesting.hacdan.org/whattoexpect/</guid><description>First time? We&amp;rsquo;re glad to help! Hope meets on Sunday mornings at the Kauffman&amp;rsquo;s house in Addison Vermont. Most days when the weather is nice, we meet outside in the front yard. Park where you can. If the grass looks safe, go for it!
Please be sure to bring a lawn chair of some sort. If you forget for whatever reason, we do have some chairs for you to sit in, it&amp;rsquo;s okay!</description></item><item><title>What We Believe</title><link>https://hcftesting.hacdan.org/whatwebelieve/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hcftesting.hacdan.org/whatwebelieve/</guid><description>We believe in these unchanging truths from the Bible The Bible is the inspired Word of God The Genesis account of creation in six literal days The sanctity of human life God eternally exists as Father, Son and Holy Spirit God loved humanity so much that He gave his Son, Jesus, virgin born, to live as a man among us and die as a sacrifice for the sin of the world, to satisfy God&amp;rsquo;s righteous demand against sin.</description></item></channel></rss>